[](https://cleanshot.cloud/)Menu

Contents

### Docs

### Security & Legal

### CleanShot Cloud

CleanShot Cloud Privacy Policy
==============================

Last update: October 1, 2024

Your privacy is important to us. We recognize trust in us as a very important part of our relationship and a key value of our business practice, in particular concerning data privacy.

This privacy statement explains the scope of personal data processed by our company Make The Web Oślizło & Magiera s.c., address: ul. Wałowa 49, 44‐300 Wodzisław Śląski (Poland), NIP: 6472582030 (“MTW”), how we process it, and for what purposes. MTW is the personal data controller. We want that to be clear for you. In case of any doubts, please contact us at [hello@cleanshot.com](mailto:hello@cleanshot.com) (this is our address as the personal data controller).

------------------------------------------------------------

You directly provided us with the data we process while registering to the application CleanShot Cloud ("Application") or for our newsletter (to which you can subscribe at [https://cleanshot.com](https://cleanshot.com/)) and using our service.

----------------------------------------------------

The personal information that we collect and process are each or every of following categories of personal data:

* E-mail address;
* First name and last name;
* Photo / avatar;
* IP address

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

We use personal data that we collected strictly for the purpose that we received it for or in our interest if it is necessary to maintain our relations or support service provided.

The purposes we can process your data are:

* providing services in application;
* contact needs;
* direct marketing of our services and products;
* ordered newsletter;
* resolving conflicts and complaints;

In such a situation, personal data is processed on the following legal grounds:

1. art. 6 par. 1 point b GDPR, because processing is necessary to take steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract and to perform this contract. In other words, in order to be able to provide you with our Services, we must have this personal data.
2. art. 6 par. 1 point a GDPR because you might have agreed to share your data with us, for example for means of receiving the newsletter. The person whose data is processed has the right to withdraw his consent to the processing of personal data at any time. Withdrawal of consent does not affect the processing that was carried out before its withdrawal. ;
3. art. 6 par. 1 point f GDPR because processing may be necessary to contact you by phone or electronic correspondence to the e-mail address provided, if questions arise regardless of the concluded contract or if it is necessary to resolve a dispute between us;

--------------------------------------------------------

CleanShot Cloud securely stores your data in electronic means only.

MTW has adopted reasonable and appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures and measures that are designed to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure appropriate use of the information provided. The personal information you provide is stored in computer systems located in controlled facilities with limited access. When we transmit confidential information over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption and other safeguards.

MTW stores your data for the period of time needed to realize the purpose that we collected them for. Once the period expires, we delete personal data or anonymize it, so its restoration is impossible.

--------------------------------------------------------

Since we operate worldwide, be informed that we might transfer collected data outside your country of residence. Please note that the data protection and other laws of countries to which your information may be transferred might differ as those in your country. Nevertheless, MTW has taken steps to ensure an adequate level of protection of your data regardless of the country where it is transferred. We transfer our data to countries or entities assuring adequate levels of protection.

We may share the information we collect with the following types of entities, including those which may be located outside your country of residence:

**Service Providers, Suppliers and Contractors.** MTW retains service providers, suppliers and contractors to manage or support our business operations, provide professional services, deliver products, services and customer solutions, and assist with our product warranties. These providers and suppliers may be located in the EU or other locations where we do business. A detailed list of our providers and suppliers is available [here](https://cleanshot.cloud/cloud/subprocessors). These parties may use the information solely in conjunction with the specific services they provide for us. We cooperate only with trustworthy contractors that provide sufficient guarantees and implement appropriate technical and organizational measures in such a manner that processing ensures protection of personal data we transfer. We base on standard contract clauses confirmed by the EU.

**For Legal Purposes.** We may disclose information to third parties for legal or compliance purposes and responsibilities, such as to protect the security of the website or to help detect fraud. We may also use collected data for the purpose of managing any kind of dispute, including litigation.

**Otherwise with Your Consent.** In addition to the sharing described or permitted by this Privacy Policy, we may share information about you with third parties if you provide consent to such sharing.

Except as described in this Policy, MTW will share your data to: (i) respond to duly authorized information requests of police and governmental authorities; (ii) comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, or court order; (iii) investigate and help prevent security threats, fraud or other malicious activity; (iv) enforce/protect the rights and properties of MTW; or (v) protect the rights or personal safety of MTW, our employees, and third parties on or using CleanShot Cloud property when allowed and in line with the requirements of applicable law.

------------------------------------------------------------------------------

**The right to access** – you have the right to request a copy of your personal data that we process. We may charge a small fee for this service.

**The right to rectification** – you have the right to request to correct any information we process about you, that you believe to be inaccurate. You also have the right to request to complete any incomplete data.

**The right to erasure** – you have the right to request erasure of your personal data. The right is not absolute and only applies in certain circumstances.

**The right to restrict processing** – you have the right to request for restricting of the scope of your personal data that we are processing. The right is not absolute and only applies in certain circumstances.

**The right to object processing** - you have the right to object to processing your data. The right is not absolute and only applies in certain circumstances.

**The right to withdraw consent** - you have the right to withdraw consent to the processing of personal data at any time. Withdrawal of consent does not affect the processing that was carried out before its withdrawal.

**The right to data portability** ­– you have the right to request to transfer the data that we have collected to another organization or directly to you. The right is not absolute and only applies in certain circumstances.

Please be informed that in order to protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to your data.

If you make a request considering aforementioned rights, please be informed that we have 30 days to respond to you and if the request is complex we can extend the period for another 2 months. If you would like to exercise one of these rights, please contact us at our e-mail: [hello@cleanshot.com](mailto:hello@cleanshot.com).

---------------------------------------------------------------

No, CleanShot Cloud does not knowingly collect information from children as defined by local law, and does not target its websites to children. If we learn that we collected any information from children, we will purge it immediately, except for responding to a question or inquiry on a one-time basis from the individual. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

No, CleanShot Cloud does not make any decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning the data subject.

----------------------------------------

If you have comments or questions about our privacy statement, or any concerns or a complaint regarding our collection and use of your personal data or a possible breach of your privacy, please email us at [hello@cleanshot.com](mailto:hello@cleanshot.com).

We treat your comments and any concerns confidentially. Our representative will contact you within a reasonable time after receipt of your inquiry to address your concerns and outline options regarding how they may be resolved. We will aim to ensure that concerns are resolved in a timely and appropriate manner.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Should you wish to report a complaint or if you feel that MTW has not addressed your concern or request in a satisfactory manner, you may lodge a complaint with your national Data Protection Authority (DPA).

----------------------------------------------------------------------------

### [Changes To This Privacy Statement](#changes-to-this-privacy-statement)

If we modify our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised statement on this subpage, with an updated revision date. If we make significant changes to our Statement that materially alter our privacy practices, we may also notify you by other means, such as posting a notice on our corporate website and/or social media pages.

### [Cookies](#cookies)

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information.

CleanShot Cloud might use cookies to help CleanShot Cloud identify and track visitors, their usage of CleanShot Cloud service, and their service access preferences. It is not possible to identify the User on the basis of cookie files, whether session or permanent. The cookie mechanism prevents collecting any personal data. The cookies used on CleanShot Cloud are safe for User’s device, in particular they prevent viruses or other software from breaking into to the device. Files generated directly by CleanShot Cloud may not be read by other websites. Third-party cookies (i.e. cookies provided by entities co-operating with the MTW) may be read by an external server.

CleanShot Cloud visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using CleanShot Cloud’s services, with the drawback that certain features of CleanShot Cloud’s services may not function properly without the aid of cookies. You can opt out cookies through the ‘Help’ function in your browser settings. For further information on cookies and how to deactivate them in your browser, we recommend that you consult the information made available to you by your browser. Alternatively, visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for comprehensive information on how to control or delete cookies in a wide variety of browsers, including how to delete cookies from your computer. For information on how to do this on your mobile device – such as a smartphone or tablet – please refer to your handset manual.

* Product

* License

* Support

* CleanShot Cloud

© Copyright [MTW](https://mtw.team/)
